cellware.com 2016-06-04

# Privacy Policy | Bidtellect

Bidtellect is a digital advertising company that may deliver advertisements to the websites or applications you visit. Bidtellect understands that your online privacy is important to you. We provide this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect from advertisements served through our Bidtellect Native Platform, a network of websites owned by third-party publishers (collectively, the “Services”) and when you visit this website, [www.bidtellect.com](http://www.bidtellect.com/) (“Website”), owned and operated by Bidtellect, Inc. (“Bidtellect”) and how such information is used and shared with third parties according to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information is gathered. We may change our Privacy Policy at any time by updating this page. We will provide you with notice of changes to our Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is provided pursuant to state and federal laws of the United States of America. Your home jurisdiction may have privacy laws that are more or less protective than those of the State of Florida, U.S.A. By continuing to use the Services or this Website or by sharing information with us, you consent to the use of your information as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Please note that this policy applies only to information collected via the Services and this Website, and not to third party websites, those of our vendors and business partners (“Service Providers”), or other companies or organizations to which the Services or Website may link. The Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time by us as further described below.

The terms “you,” “your,” and “yours” refer to visitors to our website and consumers who interact with advertisements or third party websites via the Services. The terms “Bidtellect,” “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Bidtellect and its affiliated companies (collectively, “Bidtellect”).

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND RECEIVE

Personally Identifiable Information Collected Upon Registration. If you desire access to restricted sections of the Website or to request or purchase certain products or services, you must first register and submit personally identifiable information (“PII”) to Bidtellect. You may choose not to provide PII to us by not registering on the Website. The personally identifiable information that we may collect includes:

  * your name
  * email address
  * company name
  * telephone number
  * company websites

#### Cookies and other Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

When you visit the Website, interact with the Services or our emails, we use Cookies (as described below) to automatically record non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”) about your visit, including:

  * your computer’s IP address or a mobile device’s unique ID,
  * type of browser
  * domain name or application name of referring website
  * date and time of day of access
  * your activities on the Website
  * your activities on the Services
  * your activities on other websites you visit
  * your responses to email
  * your responses to our online and mobile advertisements

#### CALIFORNIA “DO NOT TRACK” DISCLOSURES

  1. Bidtellect does not override your browser or device privacy settings without your consent.
  2. Bidtellect does not authorize third parties to collect PII or override your browser or device privacy settings without your consent.

Information collected as a result of Cookies set by third parties related to the Services is subject to and controlled by the privacy practices of such third parties and Bidtellect is not responsible for either the privacy practices of such third parties or the use of the information they collect.

#### Ad Delivery & Reporting Across Multiple Sites by the Services

As part of our ad delivery and reporting Services, we log page views and collect information for the purpose of delivering ads or providing advertising-related services, including providing a specific advertisement based on a particular type of browser or time of day; statistical reporting in connection with the activity on a website; and tracking the number of ads served on a particular day to a particular website.

To do so, we collect anonymous information about your activity on the Website, using our Services, online, and in email using small computer files that ask permission to be stored on your computer, including log files, cookies, java script or that track your activities online, etc., such as web pixels or clear gifs (collectively, “Cookies”).

Most browsers are automatically set to accept Cookies when you visit a website. You can disable Cookies in your browser or set your browser to alert you when Cookies are set. However some functions on the Website may not function properly if Cookies are disabled. To learn more about cookies, visit[www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/).

To learn how to opt-out of Cookies, visit [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### Information Obtained from Other Companies

We license and otherwise obtain Non-PII from various other companies, including research companies, data aggregation companies and other third party companies. Data sets may include information about you or your demographic segment that such companies have licensed, purchased or collected. We use this information for all the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, and for any other purpose that we chose.

European Union Users. We do not intend to collect PII from European Union users. If you are from the European Union, do not provide us with PII or use the Website. If we learn that we collected PII from a user from the European Union, we will promptly delete that information.

Children’s Privacy/Age Restriction. The Website is intended only for use by persons age 18 or over. We do not intend to collect PII from persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18 do not provide us with PII or use the Website. If we learn that we have collected PII from a person under the age of 18, we will promptly delete that information. If you believe that we collected information from a person under the age of 18, contact us at[privacy@bidtellect.com](mailto:privacy@bidtellect.com).

#### USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION

We use your PII to:

  * set up and administration of your registered user account
  * provide information about products and Services
  * provide products and Services
  * communicate about your use of the Website, products and Services
  * improve the Website and Services
  * to enforce our terms of use or to protect our rights
  * for any other purpose for which you provide consent

Email Communications and Promotional Offers. If you register for a user account, we may use your PII to send email or other communications to you that relate to administration of your user account, your use of the Website and Services, and promotional materials about products and services. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive email or communications from us, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of the communications or contact us at privacy@bidtellect.com.

#### Third-Party Contractors

We may share your information with third-party contractors and Service Providers who support the Services and Website by providing services to us or on our behalf, such as research companies, vendors, administrative service providers, technology providers, and selected partners for data validation, aggregation, enhancement, verification and suppression purposes, and for research, marketing, advertising, and data aggregation purposes. These third-party contractors will only have access to the information needed to perform these limited functions on our behalf and are required, to the extent practicable, to provide your information with at least the same level of protection and security as we use for the Website. We also may share information with advertisers, publishers and other third parties for marketing and advertising purposes, but such information does not include PII except if you provided it as part of your user registration as described above.

#### Companies that Acquire Our Business or Assets

If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, sale of assets, securities offering, bankruptcy, reorganization, dissolution, or other transaction or if the ownership of all or substantially all of our business otherwise changes, we may share or transfer your information to a third party or parties in connection with the applicable transaction.

#### Our Affiliates

We may share some or all of your information with our parent company, subsidiaries and corporate affiliates, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us. We will require these entities to comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended, with regard to their use of your PII.

Law Enforcement. We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Bidtellect or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

#### HOW WE PROTECT AND RETAIN YOUR INFORMATION

We take security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data. These include firewalls and encryption, internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices, and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems.

However, the internet and mobile web are inherently insecure and so we are unable to guarantee that the security measures we take will not be penetrated or compromised or that your information will remain secure under all circumstances.

If we retain personally identifiable information (‘PII”) on our systems, we restrict access to PII to employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our Websites, products and services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination, if they fail to meet these obligations.

Currently, Bidtellect retains Non-PII collected to report ad delivery (see, “Ad Delivery & Reporting” above) for up to six (6) months. However, other Non-PII stored in Cookies or in aggregate statistics, reports and summaries regarding ad delivery, and PII in registered user accounts may be retained indefinitely.

Bidtellect reserves the right to delete any or all Non-PII or PII that relates to you at any time and in Bidtellect’s sole discretion, notwithstanding its normal data retention policies. If Bidtellect changes its retention data policies by updating this Privacy Policy, its new policies will apply to all data then retained by Bidtellect.

#### HOW TO CONTROL AND CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION

#### Bidtellect Opt-Out

Bidtellect is committed to providing consumers notice and choice regarding online and mobile privacy. If you wish to opt-out of data collection by Bidtellect’s Cookies, please use our opt-out tool at <http://www.bidtellect.com/optout>.

Our opt-out tool is a Cookie that will honor your privacy preferences for 5 years or longer in our discretion. If you use multiple Internet browsers or other users share your computer, the opt-out process should be done for each browser and/or user login. If you clear Cookies or browser history from your computer, or your anti-virus or other software clears Cookies from your computer, then you will need to repeat the opt-out process. The opt-out tool does not work if your browser is set to ignore cookies.

To opt out of Cookies from other websites or companies please visit the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website at[www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). To opt out of Cookies in advertisements use the Ad Option icon in the ad, or visit the DAA website at<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

#### Your Account

You may access and correct personal information in your user account profile. If you registered to use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account login and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. We reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in their sole discretion.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents who have an established business relationship with us have the right to request that we provide certain information regarding the disclosure of their personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year. You may send your request for such information to privacy@bidtellect.com Requests shall only be accepted via this email address. We shall not be responsible for requests made over the telephone or by any other means.

#### Modification of this Privacy Policy

Bidtellect may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the effective date (found at the top). It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, and we encourage you to visit this page often. By continuing to use the Services or this Website or by sharing information with us, you consent to the use of your information as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

#### CONTACT US:

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, contact:

> Attn: Chief Compliance Officer
> 
> Bidtellect
> 
> 777 East Atlantic Ave, Suite 312
> 
> Delray Beach, Florida 33483
> 
> Tel.: 561-303-1300
> 
> Fax.: 561-892-3744
> 
> Email: [privacy@bidtellect.com](mailto:privacy@bidtellect.com)
